It's all in who you trust
The Big Bounce is a comedy, crime film directed by George Armitage.
A small-time con artist and a Hawaiian real estate developer's mischievous,
enterprising mistress team up for a potential $200,000 score.
Jack Ryan, played by Owen Wilson.
Walter Crewes, played by Morgan Freeman.
Ray Ritchie, played by Gary Sinise.
Nancy Hayes, played by Sara Foster.
Joe Lurie, played by Willie Nelson.
Lou Harris, played by Vinnie Jones.
The Big Bounce is a 2004 American comedy heist film starring Owen
Wilson, Charlie Sheen, Sara Foster and Morgan Freeman.
It was directed by George Armitage in his final directing role.
It is based on the 1969 novel of the same name by Elmore Leonard.
Leonard's novel had previously been adapted for the big screen in a 1969 film of
the same name directed by Alex March and starring Ryan O'Neal.
The film explores themes of hotel, robbery, based
on novel or book, judge, blackmail.
The tone is lighthearted.